# Pedro Primor

+351 961241116 | primor.pedro@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/pedroprimor/

#### ABOUT

Computer engineering student currently enrolled at NOVA SST in Lisbon for the final year of my master's degree. Experience in front-end web development and mobile game development but open to expand my professional expertise to other fields of computer science.

#### **EDUCATION**

# NOVA School of Science and Technology Integrated Master in Computer Science Sep. 2017 – Present Technische Universität Dresden Erasmus+ Programme Exchange Period Lisbon, Portugal Sep. 2017 – Present Dresden, Germany Apr. 2021 – Oct. 2021

#### EXPERIENCE

#### Front-end Developer and QA Assistant

Jul. 2019 – Aug. 2019

Automatication MJM

Lisbon, Portugal

- Developed React components to display the result of some unit tests on a web page
- Experimented with AWS Amplify's authentication mechanism
- Learned to develop unit tests for JavaScript environments using JEST

#### Front-end Developer Intern

Apr. 2020 – Jul. 2020

Altitude Software

Lisbon, Portugal

- Developed React components to replace existing ASP.NET components in a contact centers management platform
- Integrated the components with the application's back-end using C# and ASP.NET

## Projects

### My Spelling Game | Unity, C#, SQLite

Jul. 2018 - Nov. 2018

• Developed a 2D mobile game for Android/iOS along with a graphic designer

#### EVENTS

Unity Workshop - JORTEC Informática 2019   $Unity, C\#$	Feb. 2019
Android Training Program   Android Studio, Java, Kotlin	Nov. 2019

#### Languages

Proficient: Portuguese, English Begginer: Spanish, German

#### TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: Java, Python, C#, SQL (SQLite), HTML/CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, OCaml, Kotlin

Frameworks: React, Redux, Flutter

Developer Tools: Git, webpack, npm, VS Code, Visual Studio, PyCharm, IntelliJ, Eclipse, Android Studio, Unity

Libraries: Material-UI, pandas, NumPy, Matplotlib, scikit-learn, OpenCV